I know what you've been doing. Franklin.
I know it's not just weed anymore.
You know how I feel about all of this.
You're welcome home
when you stop.
Not too long ago. you were happy
with just a few hundred dollars.
How we grow. huh?
- Avi!
- What...
- LAPD!
- Don't move!
Hello. officer.
I'll have the first load
in the next couple of days.
She also tell you I'm done
paying the other tax?
The tax stays.
Unless you want
the streets to know
it was us that hit your family.
Cops were clearing an empty lot.
Alton didn't want to leave.
He's through the worst
of the detox.
but if he gets put back
chances are he runs right back
to the bottle.
Chances are good of that
no matter where he goes.
I'm done.
Think that old bitch can
satisfy you the way I do?
She can do ten times what
you ever could.
We started this.
Can't do this without you.
You gonna have to try.
We retaliate. prison esés
be after all of us.
Here's the deal I'm willing
to make with you.
If you can figure out who did it
then we can talk about payback.
Her name is Soledad.
I brought her 'cause
we're gonna get married.
This is an immigration raid!
I got the paperwork.
Puto!
INS thing end up doing
what you hoped?
The ice queen
was very impressed.
She's starting to let me in.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Here.
No.
Synced & corrected by MaxPayne
== https://subscene.com ==
Race you.
Come on.
Money. Money. Money.
Want some more?
What the fuck?
- Avi.
- Franklin.
You see?
Money does fall from the sky.
Gimme one too!
Get out the street. now!
Mmm. Randy's donut.
You should have gotten
a full dozen. Frankie.
I hear you can afford it.
Got my men to look around
the neighborhood.
Seems you been selling
those little rocks of yours everywhere.
I'm glad to see my absence
didn't inconvenience you.
Yeah. well. my business can't stop
just 'cause you got taken off the board.
I'm not mad that you found
a new supplier. Frankie.
You know why I'm not mad?
Why?
Because you and me.
we're going back
to business as usual.
Back to selling good product
at good prices.
I scratch your balls.
You scratch mine.
You know...
My old supplier.
he was so sweet.
Like a virgin in a whorehouse.
But you know what. Frankie?
I'm not going to even ask you
if it is my virgin
you're fucking.
I know it's not.
It can't be.
Because if it is.
I-I get nervous
and-and start wondering
how convenient is it
that Franklin was there
when the cops arrived
at my house
and he was the only one
that got away.
I got an appointment
with the guy who gave me up.
Gonna pour gasoline down
his throat and light a match.
but...
next week!
You and I.
We're going back to business.
Same deal as before.
My new place and number.
Nice catching up. Frankie.
I'll see you soon.
Yuda.
How the hell he get out anyway?
My guess would be
that he cut some kind
of deal with the feds.
That house is full
of drugs and guns.
What kind of deal
Avi make gets him back
on the street doing
the same shit he went in for?
He's rich.
and he's white.
and that's just the deal.
Yeah. well. maybe I'm the deal?
Maybe that motherfucker's out
so he can set me up.
Maybe next time I see him.
he's wearing a wire.
You think that motherfucker
gonna let me frisk him?
Come on.
You're being
a little bit paranoid.
I'm a black man in America.
God damn it.
Hell. yeah. I'm paranoid.
You know. people of
your complexion
don't exactly have
the best record
when it comes to dealing
with people like me.
And it when it comes down to it.
white people be afraid of blacks.
but it should be
the other way around.
Mr. Kidnapper.
Look.
Let me look into it.
And how you gonna do that?
Let's just say that...
an LAPD paycheck
doesn't go very far.
Sometimes cops need help.
Even is Avi ain't trying
to set me up.
he's still crazy.
Might have to take
him up on his offer
just so I can sleep at night.
You can't go back. man.
He told me he's on his way
to kill the dude he thought
sold him out.
and when Avi talks like that.
he's not being funny.
He's being real.
Just let me reach out to him.
I got a feeling I can get him
to leave you alone.
How?
There's some things
that's probably better
you don't know.
Right. Yeah.
Right. and I should wear
my helmet when I ride my bike.
look both ways
when I cross the street.
Come on. Franklin.
I gotta be there when you go.
Reed.
Or I go back
to working with Avi. man.
It's up to you.
We show up together. he's
gonna know you betrayed him.
I can't protect you then.
So don't you think it's best
if he hears it from us?
See you soon. Reed.
- Bye.
- Ciao.
Hola.
Actually. yes.
Reed's coming to pick up
his product today
so when he shows up
I'm gonna need you
to help him with
these crates out to his...
No Reed today?
Something happened.
I hope that's not a problem.
Not as long you like avocados.
If the quantity is right
I like 'em plenty.
Oh. No. No. No. No. No.
No. No. No.
I got it.
Allow me.
Right in the back. guys.
Thank you.
So you're the one who flies
the loads in. right?
Uh. I've been known to fly
a little from time to time.
You know. Soledad's never
been in a plane.
Are you curious?
You wanna give it a try?
Here's your chance.
Matt can be your first time.
I don't know.
First times are not always fun.
Well. I have never
had a girl complain
to me about being her first.
She's great company.
You should take her with you
on one of your Colombia trips.
Help pass the time.
I'm game if you are.
Maybe we should
start with something
a little closer to home.
What do you say?
Okay.
I'll let you know.
Looking forward to it.
Ladies.
I did not appreciate that.
I'm just playing him.
By using me to lead him on.
Mm-mm.
He's gonna give up
his supplier
before he tries to fuck you.
Just keep working him.
You did great. by the way.
What the hell are you looking for?
Oh. Uh...
I was gonna make a egg salad.
but you out of mustard.
You thought I was
looking for booze.
didn't you?
No.
I threw all that out
the night you moved in.
Anyway. I don't time for lunch.
Wait.
Now. uh...
Listen. I know it can't be easy
with me being here.
Extra mouth to feed and all.
Well. how are you doing
with the bills?
Mortgage.
There's a...
I want to be able to
try and help out if you need it.
The only thing I need
is to finish getting dressed
so I'm not late.
Renny?
Know what you want. huh?
Uh-huh. that shit feel good.
don't it?
Ow!
Stop. We going in.
Fuck.
You like that shit. woman?
What's raw is the stank
coming off your black ass.
You told me no one was
fucking here.
Nigga. I was fucking.
You call that fucking?
Look like you was playing leap frog.
Where Kevin at?
- The fuck I know.
- He's your boy.
He my boy. not my boyfriend.
you fruitcake motherfucker.
Hey. watch your mouth.
li'l nigga.
Only know how to use your dick.
- Yo. fuck you.
- Fuck you.
- Baby.
- Don't baby me.
Hey. girl.
Yeah. she did.
She's just jealous.
Can I help you?
- Like help with what?
- What you doing here?
What you doing here?
Excuse me?
Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
Talk for a minute. Kev.
Una momenta. you know.
'Sup with the Mexicans?
I just came by
to get some special smoke
for the girls. man.
You know my thing
about that thing.
Doing your thing.
or doing your thing?
Now I told you
I was gonna found out
who did this shit. right.
Just be careful.
These girls don't play.
I'm always careful
with the pussy. Saint.
Andale!
- Hey. somebody get that shit!
- Yeah. I hear you.
Yeah?
Hey. it's Peaches.
Kevin ain't here
at the cook house.
and nigga supposed to help me
re-up the truck.
Yeah. Yeah.
he handling some shit.
I send Jerome over
to roll with you.
Hold tight.
All right.
Hey. Unc!
I'ma need you to help Peaches
out at the cook house.
You hear me?
Yeah. I hear you. nigga!
Gimme a minute!
What the fuck?
Hey. can we talk?
I'm sorry. what?
No. We ain't got nothing
to talk about.
What you doing here?
I'm busy right now.
Please leave.
It's your mother.
What about her?
Well. it's the house.
She's three months behind.
I think she's gonna lose...
What the fuck you know
about the house?
Well. I had a little accident
and she took me in.
- Took you in? What?
- Fuck you. Jerome.
You said we was going
to Fatburger.
No. I said.
"I was gonna go to Fatburger."
You was gonna take
your ass home.
Oh. so it's like that?
What y'all stupid ass niggas
looking at?
Don't even think
about calling me.
'Scuse me.
Jerome.
New friend of yours?
You know how it is.
Everything all right?
You high. man?
If I was high.
you'd know it. man.
Go help Peaches.
What up. man?
Hold up.
somebody say you can come in?
Hey. hold on now.
I didn't come here
to talk about me.
I saw the notices this morning.
But if you wanted
to help your mama out.
- You have the means.
- Oh. I see. Yeah.
There it is.
So I give you the money
and you just gonna go give
it to my moms. huh?
No. No. It ain't like that.
Been like that since
I was old enough to know
what the word "deadbeat" meant.
Now listen.
I said my piece.
Now you do what you want.
I will.
Nice shoes.
Tell me what you think
of this one.
It's got a longer runway.
better coverage on approach
and still easily accessible
by Jeep.
Hmm.
I think I could get it in here.
What's with the hesitation?
Is there anti-aircraft
in the canopy?
Look. it's not like
I'm not having fun here.
I am.
But this was supposed
to be temporary.
You remember?
So now in addition
to coke from Colombia
you want to start delivering
guns to Honduras
and add that to the mix?
- Hey. Matt?
- Yeah?
If you're thinking about leaving
this would be a very bad time.
Well. is there gonna be
a good time?
Well. yeah.
when we've won the war.
- I have a life to get back to.
- Come on.
What?
- I mean. I saw your life.
- What?
It's cutting up jackpots
with local barflies.
Wow.
You're a fucking asshole.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm an asshole.
But. look.
You're not just a pilot.
You... I trust you.
You're good at this.
You're good at all this.
and you're better at talking
to people than I am.
I need you.
Oh.
Then why don't
you stop insulting me
and start asking me questions
about how I can make this work.
Okay. yes. you're right.
I'm sorry.
What is it that you need?
Please. tell me.
I need more money.
And not just for Dad.
But to start up my own thing
when this all ends.
- Your own thing?
- Yeah.
I want to start
a skydiving school.
Are you kidding?
Why would I be kidding?
I get paid
to fly airplanes
and jump out of them.
I can't think of anything
better than that.
Okay. yeah. No. yeah.
I mean. whatever you need
you got it.
Is that it?
And no more dead bodies.
Moving them.
Disposing of them. Nothing.
You want me to fly?
That's what I agree to.
Yeah?
Yeah. of course.
And the plane.
When this done
I'm taking the plane home.
You can buy another one.
Okay. Now you're pushing it.
All right. you have fun.
Okay. fine.
You can take the plane.
Is that it?
Boy. it sounds like
you need me. huh.
Oh. God. Here we go.
We should just say
I'm essential.
Yeah. let's say that.
The best big brother
a guy could have.
A crackerjack pilot.
A world-renowned cocksman.
Okay. we're done here.
Is it true Alton's back
at the house?
- We'll talk later.
- We could talk right now.
It's none of your business
who I let into my house.
- Excuse me.
- It's my business when he
comes at me asking for handouts.
You know he tried to say
it was for you?
Some bullshit about you losing
the house?
Miss. Miss.
Just a second.
You know he's only there
to take advantage of you.
You know that. right?
- Miss! Miss.
- Mama.
Come get it!
Sissy. order's up.
Miss. I want more coffee.
Here's your fucking coffee.
Sissy. is everything okay?
Everything's fine.
He can't be staying there.
You'll have no say
about my life.
He hasn't changed.
I don't give a fuck about
how clean he look.
Just remember.
I used to lay in bed all night
listening to you cry over him.
Now he's the only reason
I'm not crying
in my bed every night.
Sissy. you got another order.
Thank you. ma'am.
Franklin was late.
I'm surprised the lady witch
doctor didn't warn you.
You know I'm just teasing you.
right?
You don't believe in anything
higher do you?
Okay. fine.
How did it go really?
Is our future looking bright?
She warned me.
You see how it curves?
It means don't trust
short Mexican women.
Especially the ones
whose names rhyme with sandia.
Pedro. Soledad.
We have two hours to get
everything ready for pickup.
Okay. you see this?
These numbers do not match.
I think we missing
a case of Hennessy.
- A whole damn box.
- Yeah.
Somebody about to
get their ass beat.
Sure hope
y'all ain't talking about me.
Hey.
- What's happening. handsome?
- How you doing?
- Hey.
- Good.
Make a phone call
about this Henny.
Don't leave without
saying good-bye.
Mm! Oh. we missed you
for Christmas.
You missed me
or you missed my cooking?
Both.
- Wanda Bell stepped up.
- Okay.
Girl think if she can
cook crack she can cook ham.
Well. I ain't sorry
I missed that.
How was your holiday?
It was the shit.
Claudia took me to New York.
- New York. for real?
- Yes.
Shopping on Fifth Avenue.
the tree at Rockefeller Center.
And freezing yo' ass off.
We managed to keep warm.
It was amazing.
We went out every night.
The Danceteria in Manhattan.
Man. we trying bring
some of that
New York flavor up in here.
You okay?
Shit ain't been the same
since you left.
Avi's out of jail
showing up at the house.
Alton moved back in
with my moms.
Jerome's a mess.
Franklin.
There ain't no
calm voice in the mix.
You know. no center.
But if you was there
it'd be perfect.
Franklin.
If you want to come here
and catch up. baby.
I am always happy to see you.
But don't do this.
You're really happy?
As I've ever been.
The world is opening up.
Then I'm happy for you.
Mm. thank you.
I love you. Franklin.
Love you too.
Then we'll see you soon. okay?
Mm-hmm.
Maybe. Maybe you'll see me.
Maybe? We better.
Q-vo. Oso?
Where's the party at?
Close the door.
'Sup. Pedro?
Fuck you been up to?
Been meaning to ask.
How's the familia?
Fuck you know about my family?
- Or what?
- I'm not talking to you.
This is Las Monarcas familia
right here.
Las Monarcas control everything.
It's just you.
these two and the puta.
No mas. what Gabriella lets you.
I'm gonna carve my placa
in your neck.
And you're gonna let me.
Ah!
Lucia.
Fuck.
Pedro.
Flatten some boxes.
Put them on the floor
in the office.
Wasn't my plan to see him.
So what?
It just happened?
It did.
And it definitely wasn't
my plan for him
to track you down.
But he did
at my job.
You didn't think he'd have
a reaction seeing you?
Learning that you're
staying here.
Yeah. well. I said I'm sorry.
Excuse me. I ain't done
speaking my mind.
He caused a scene. Alton.
I could have gotten fired.
I was wrong.
I admit it.
But I've seen the notices.
You're an inch away
from losing this place.
Now.
I've already been to the VA.
and it's gonna take a while
for me to reclaim my benefits.
What I was thinking...
Franklin ain't no savior.
Well. your brother...
I'm not gonna take
no drug money handout.
You're willing
to lose this house?
Yes. I would fucking lose
this house!
Well...
I'm sorry.
I thought I was helping.
Hey. you've done...
You done right by me.
Nurse me back to life and...
I'm gonna send you what I can
when the benefits
start to come in.
But I refuse to be
more of a burden to you
than I've been already. so...
tomorrow. I'm gonna move out.
But thank you
for everything.
You are quite a woman.
And it's not like
I didn't know that before.
Alton. wait.
You're such a goddamn man.
Hunt and gather
and all that bullshit.
Really. you are.
You have never been less
of a burden to me
in your entire life.
Why don't you go get the...
ground beef out
of the freezer to thaw.
I'll finish changing and...
We'll make dinner.
Get him the fuck out
of my sight.
Can we talk about this?
I treated you like a son.
I opened my home.
my heart to you
and this is how you pay me back?
- No.
- I approached him.
I had to convince him
that it was in his best interest
to do business with me.
Then he's all yours.
Good luck with those pebbles.
I'm sure our paths will cross.
What's that supposed to mean?
Whatever you want it to mean.
You're a big man now.
Don't fucking touch my rib eye.
What the fuck
do you know about guns?
Well. I know that you cut
a deal with the ATF.
That's why you're walking free
right now.
Oh. really?
What's the deal?
You gave someone up.
Right?
And judging by
this very nice hotel suite
and all the extra security
you got
I'm guessing it was someone big.
I mean. I'm surprised
you're still in Los Angeles
if I'm honest.
Why are we even
talking about this?
I am very much like you. Avi.
I am a man...
of eclectic interests.
So I'm thinking if you got
a little wriggle room
in this deal
that you cut maybe we could
help each other out.
Only place I don't have
wriggle room is in my shorts.
What do you need?
Handguns. assault rifles.
submachines.
All you can get.
In bulk.
I can get an awful lot.
Well. then I'm going to make
you a very rich man.
You're getting my dick hard.
Reed.
Here's the thing.
I don't care where you get 'em.
I only care that they are not
U.S.-made
and that you can deliver them
somewhere outside the country
where I can pick them up
and fly them out.
You have a place in mind?
Yeah. I hear that Panama
is nice this time of year.
Panama is pretty nice
all year round. actually.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Good to know.
You understand that if we
do this. it's by the book.
I need you to be dependable.
None of this cowboy bullshit.
When have you known me
not to be dependable?
I set this up.
you better have the money
to back it.
'Cause the people I use...
They don't get their money.
it's your name I'm giving them.
Those. from Panama.
those guns.
They make their way
some place interesting?
- Let's go.
- No.
Not till Avi tells me we good.
You broke my heart. kid.
But when a bird grows hair
on its balls...
he's gotta leave the nest!
Just like that. huh?
So we good?
What can I say?
My generosity knows
no boundaries.
I just said
I'll take care of it!
I haven't shot a gun in years.
I learned from my father.
We used to hunt the javelinas
that'd come into our backyard.
We didn't even kill
for sport or food.
He just hated them.
You saved my life.
We are family now.
That is what we do.
I don't know about this.
Nobody comes here.
Andale.
How the fuck you squash it?
It was Reed.
Pulled Avi aside and spoke
to him alone in a room.
I don't know what he said.
but that Reed got connections.
Pretty sure he got at least
one cop on the payroll.
Are you surprised
that the LAPD is corrupt?
Hell. nah.
Just never expect to see
that shit except the movies.
What's up. Kev?
Hey. what the fuck happened
to y'all?
Some shit with
the Mexican girls.
Yeah. we can see that.
Is you being careful
with the ladies?
Wait. I'm sorry.
Did you ask me
to come let you know
how it went?
This is how it went.
What?
You don't think I can find
those Mexican motherfuckers?
Think I'm too stupid?
Not as good as
the great holy Saint.
Yeah. think the whole fucking
thing's too stupid.
I mean.
look at y'all motherfuckers.
Man. this is a fucking joke.
Do you think this is a game?
No. I don't think it's
a fucking game. Saint.
You don't? Then why you
acting like a fucking idiot?
This shit ends tonight.
No more barrio manhunts.
It's done.
Saint.
Saint!
It's done.
- Saint. ain't nobody...
- It's done.
Stupid motherfuckers. man.
Salud.
Better than any painkiller.
And when Stomper
doesn't show up...
They will come.
We need to clean that room
by morning.
- Oh. really?
- Soledad. help Pedro.
I need to talk to Oso
for a second.
Mm-hmm.
E Soledad...
Gracias.
No more shipments.
No more crack.
She's a fucking cop.
Or DEA.
But definitely the law.
The way she held that gun.
The way she stood.
She didn't miss a fucking shot.
That's muscle memory.
Then how are we not in jail?
Because she's building
a case. Oso.
Getting us. she wants more
than she already has.
Our distributors.
La Fuerza.
All of us.
Either way. we're fucked.
Okay.
If she's a cop...
What does that make Pedro?
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today